ripplecoinnews.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy

This **privacy policy** supervises the approach using which [ripplecoinnews.com](https://ripplecoinnews.com/) collects, consumes, stores and release any personal or non personal information which is collected from the users interacting with our website.

 **PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION**

Website is available in Public domain and is accessible by anyone and everyone without revealing any personal information. However, when the person interacts with our site by registering, signing up for newsletter, we may ask for applicable personal information such as Name, email address.

 **NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION**

Our website uses Cookies which captures Non Personal Information about the person interacting with our site ripplecoinnews.com. Non personal information is purely the information restricted to browser details, IP address, Location, Browsing Device address and other technical information. 

 **HOW WE MAY USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION**

  * Answer Your Query via email
  * Sending Email Newsletter 
  * Use For Remarketing/Retargeting Purposes

 **INFORMATION PROTECTION**

We take User data protection very seriously. Any user data collected is always stored on secured servers with controlled and restricted access. None of the data is sold to 3rd party; however, we do share the user data with our marketing partners who help us with our various marketing activities. 

 **COOKIES**

We use cookies on our website for smooth functioning, marketing purposes and storing registered user information 

 **COOKIES WHICH WE USE ON OUR WEBSITE**

ripplecoinnews.com may use following types of cookies to improve the user experience and communication with our website:

 **Analytics cookies:** This cookies tracks user’s activity on our website, it helps us in making better marketing decisions. Analytics cookies only stores non-personal information

 **Service cookies:** Service cookie helps us to make our website work proficiently by storing user’s registration information as and when necessary, this cookie also stores the users’ browsing preferences, and keep track of the website pages that the user visits.

 **REFUSING COOKIES**

Most browsers allow you to reject/disable to accept cookies.  You can do so by visiting your browser’s privacy settings.

Blocking cookies may have a negative impact upon the usability of some sections of our website.

 **REMARKETING**

Users May Find Ads of Our Website or Services Displayed on other websites that they frequently visit. These Ads are delivered by Our Remarketing/Retargeting Partners including but Not limited to Facebook & Google. Remarketing uses Dark Cookies to Collect Users’ Non Personal Information. Please visit [Facebook Cookies Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/) & [Google Cookie Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies) For More Info. 

 **THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Users may find links to other 3rd party websites on our website including but not limited to advertisers, sponsors, and affiliates. These links are redirected to 3rd party websites which have their own sets of privacy policies which are not controlled by this Privacy Policy. Users are requested to check these policies on their own before making any decisions.

 **ADVERTISEMENTS**

Users may find advertisements on our website in the form of link, text, banner, graphics, videos etc. These 3rd party ads are delivered by our advertising partners including but not limited to Google. These links are connected to 3rd party websites which have their own sets of policies and which are not controlled by the policies on this page. 

 **THIRD-PARTY DISCLOSURE**

We never sell, trade, or otherwise provide access to the Personal Data of Users to any 3rd parties. This excludes our Affiliates & Marketing Partners. In An Event of National Security, We may also provide unrestricted access to this stored information to the Government.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve all rights to modify this privacy policy any time without any prior notice. We Update the Bottom date of the Privacy Page whenever We make a Change. You are advised to check the date and review the Policy accordingly.

 **YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using [**ripplecoinnews.com**](https://ripplecoinnews.com/), You hereby agree to have Accepted this Privacy Policy. In Case You do not agree, you should immediately stop using this website.

 **CONTACTING US**

if you have any concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us by visiting [**Contact Page**](https://ripplecoinnews.com/contact-us) at ripplecoinnews.com or you can email us at [admin@ripplecoinnews.com](mailto:contact@ripplecoinnews.com) ** **

Last updated on 7 April 2018
